Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series V: Administrative Files
  - Trotter, Joe William - "Introduction" from Black Migration in Historical Perspective, 1991
  - Roberts, Dorothy - Killing the Black Body, 150-201, 1997
  - Said, Edward - Orientalism Intro and Afterword, 1979
  - Pascoe, Peggy - "Gender Systems in Conflict: The Marriages of Mission-Educated Chinese American Women" Unequal Sisters, 1989
  - Omi, Michael and Howard Winant Racial Formation in the US, 1986
  - Slave Routes Press Releases, 1999
  - Slave Routes Fundraising, 1999
  - Yari Yari, 1997-2004
  - Slave Routes - Photo Prints, 1999
  - Slave Routes - Proposals, 1999
  - Slave Routes - Dinner, 1999
  - Slave Routes - Travel Arrangments, 1999
  - Slave Routes - Press Lists, 1999
  - Slave Routes - Speakers Information, 1999
  - Slave Routes - Bios, 1999
  - Haiti on Screen, 2004
  - France in Africa/Africa in France Flyers, 1998-1999
  - Artist in Residence - Misc., 1997-1998
  - Calendars, 1998
  - Walter Mosley - Always Outnumbered, 1998
  - Florence Project, 1997-1998
  - Black Genius - Programmatic, 1997-1998
  - Black Genius - Meetings, 1997-1998
  - Black Genius - Participants, 1997-1998
  - Black Genius - Flyers/Brochures, 1997-1998
  - Faculty Reading - Scenarios and Briefing, 1998
  - Core Faculty, 1998
  - Faculty, 1996-1997
  - Fanon Conference, 1997-1998
  - From Conceptualization to Realization, 1997-1998
  - Press Releases, 1998
  - France in Africa/Africa in France - Maryse Conde, 1998
  - France in Africa/African in France - Henri Lopes, 1998
  - Thulani Davis/Artist & Society November 6 Event, 1998
  - Slave Routes - Save the Date, 1999
  - Artist in Residence - Danny Glover - Toussaint L'Ovuverture October 19 1998
  - Slave Routes, 1999
  - Thulani Davis/Artist & Society March 26 Event, 1998
  - Press Clippings, 1999
  - Artist in Residence - Danny Glover - Actors Workshop October 13 1998
  - Distinguished Scholar in Residence - Wole Soyinka - Dinner, 1998-1999
  - Slave Routes - Shango, 1999
  - Projects - End of the Year Report, 1998
  - The Many Colors of HipHop, 1998
  - Student Request & Funding Spring 1999
  - African Film Festival, 1999
  - Career Day, 1993
  - AEJ Summer Internship, 1993
  - Promotional Materials, 1993-1995
  - Promotional Materials, 1994
  - Henry Louis Gates, 1993
  - Promotional Materials, 1993
  - Modern Days Ancient Nights Film Festival, 1994
  - Women's History Month Lecture: Dr. Betty Shabazz, 1993
  - Black Thought in Progress Lecture Series - Ali Mazrui, 1994
  - Black Thought in Progress Lecture Series - Quincy Troupe, 1995
  - Black Cinema, 1994
  - Black Thought in Progress Lecture Series - Patricia Hill Collins, 1995
  - African Art Symposium, 1995
  - Promotional Materials, 1995-1997
  - Black Thought, 1996-1996
  - Angela Davis (Press), 1993-1994
  - Clippings, 1996-1997
  - Promotional Materials, 1998
  - Promotional Materials, 1999-2000
  - Promotional Materials, 2002